{
    "id": "yuikuroki",
    "name": "黒木結",
    "yomi": "Yui Kuroki",
    "text": [
        "京都で現代美術の作品を作っています。",
        "I am a contemporary artist based Kyoto."
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Tumblr",
            "href": "https://yui-kuroki.tumblr.com/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "What do you look at when you taking a walk?",
            "jp": "さんぽ中、つい見てしまうのは？",
            "yes": "plants at house around",
            "left": "人の家の植物",
            "no": "window of a house",
            "right": "人の家の窓"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "When you sleep lights are?",
            "jp": "寝る時、電気を消す？",
            "yes": "Off",
            "left": "消す",
            "no": "On",
            "right": "消さない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "What bedding do you use?",
            "jp": "いつも使う寝具は",
            "yes": "Bed",
            "left": "ベッド",
            "no": "Futon",
            "right": "敷布団"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Do you like walking?",
            "jp": "歩くのは好き？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Do you dream?",
            "jp": "よく夢を",
            "yes": "often",
            "left": "見る",
            "no": "rarely",
            "right": "見ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "What would you do when you visit a town you don't know?",
            "jp": "知らない場所に行ったら",
            "yes": "walking around",
            "left": "町を散歩する",
            "no": "looking for a cafe",
            "right": "喫茶店を探す"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Do you usually use a pillow?",
            "jp": "寝る時、枕を使う？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "使う",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "使わない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Do you good at remembering directions?",
            "jp": "道を覚えるのは得意？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "What do you tend to do when you take a walk?",
            "jp": "散歩中よくすることは？",
            "yes": "listening to music",
            "left": "音楽を聴く",
            "no": "thinking about something",
            "right": "考えごと"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Have you ever slept outdoor?",
            "jp": "屋外で寝たことある？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "ない"
        }
    ]
}